The End
Remember whispers in the dark Just a flicker,
not a spark A house of shadows, paper thin Never
knew where to begin You came along as guiding
light And turned the darkness into bright You
found the key, you built the door A thing we never
had before
And in this house on Lisa Court You built our one
and only port A steady roof, a solid floor You
gave us that and so much more Yeah, in this house
on Lisa Court You are our rock, our last resort
You gave us a place to finally live With your
loving,
steady hand
The simple sound of your car key Is the sound of
safety wild and free The smell of dinner on the
stove A testament to your true love No need to
hide, no need to brace In this quiet, gentle,
sacred space You drew a line against the past A
sanctuary built to last And in this house on Lisa
Court You built our one and only fort A steady
roof, a solid floor You gave us that and so much
more Yeah, in this house on Lisa Court You are our
rock, our last resort You gave us a place to
finally land With your loving, steady hand.
And in this house on Lisa Court You built our one
and only fort A steady roof, a solid floor You
gave us that and so much more Yeah, and in this
house on Lisa Court You are our rock, our last
resort You gave us a place to finally lay With
your loving,
steady hand.